[
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62602d414b176d54800e3c8a",
        "correctAnswer": "Canada",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Australia",
            "New Zealand",
            "United States"
        ],
        "question": "Where would you find the city of Vancouver?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62373602cfe13103f55eb591",
        "correctAnswer": "The United Kingdom",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Ukraine",
            "Uzbekistan",
            "Uganda"
        ],
        "question": "Which region of the world uses '.uk' at the end of its web addresses?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62602d8f4b176d54800e3ca1",
        "correctAnswer": "Thailand",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Indonesia",
            "Mongolia",
            "South Korea"
        ],
        "question": "In which country is the city of Bangkok?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "623384d462eaad73716a8c33",
        "correctAnswer": "The SaharaÂ ",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Gobi",
            "The Mojave",
            "The Arabian"
        ],
        "question": "What Is The Worlds Largest Hot Desert?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62602e064b176d54800e3cbc",
        "correctAnswer": "Napoli",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Dublin",
            "Leipzig",
            "Athens"
        ],
        "question": "Which of these cities is in Italy?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62602d4b4b176d54800e3c8d",
        "correctAnswer": "Israel",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Lebanon",
            "Egypt",
            "Qatar"
        ],
        "question": "In which country is the city of Tel Aviv?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "62602db64b176d54800e3ca8",
        "correctAnswer": "The Hague",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Paris",
            "Prague",
            "Rome"
        ],
        "question": "Which of these cities is in Netherlands?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950acf",
        "correctAnswer": "Pakistan",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Tajikistan",
            "Kyrgyzstan",
            "Thailand"
        ],
        "question": "Which of these countries borders India?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "6237408acb85f7ce9e949d09",
        "correctAnswer": "Greece",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Luxembourg",
            "Georgia",
            "Serbia"
        ],
        "question": "Athens is the capital city of which country?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "id": "623b5834fd6c701a921183a4",
        "correctAnswer": "Russia",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Bosnia & Herzegovina",
            "Greece",
            "Sweden"
        ],
        "question": "In which country would you find the city of Saint Petersburg?",
        "difficulty": "easy"
    }
]